stewartmedia.biz 2018-06-30

# Privacy Policy | StewArt Media

Stew Art Media values the privacy of our subscribers and we despise spamming on the Internet. Spamming costs the people who receive it time and money. We comply with the National Privacy Principles as set out in the Privacy Act when providing the services here at Stew Art Media

**1\. The information we collect**

a) We may collect information about you (including but not limited to) such as your name, contact details, e-mail addresses, payment details etc. as necessary when you create an account or other pages on this web site. 

b) Payment Information  
At time of payment, information is passed securely using a third party gateway. We do not collect or store credit card information.

**2\. How do we use this information?**

We will not use or disclose your information except where such disclosure is required by law. We will only use your personal information for the following purposes:  
* Providing Stew Art Media services;  
* Notifying you of additional features or services, and if we do so without your consent you may request to receive no such communication;  
* Responding to any enquiries from you;  
* To third parties where such disclosure is reasonably necessary to enable us to provide our services.

**3\. Can I access my personal information?**

You can access the personal information that we hold about you by contacting the Privacy Officer as set out below. We will provide you with access to your personal information unless we are legally authorised to refuse your request. We may charge a reasonable amount for providing access.

**4\. How secure is my personal information?**

We will use all reasonable endeavours to keep your personal information secure. Notwithstanding the above, the Internet is not a secure medium and we will no be held responsible over loss of personal information in transit via the Internet.

**5\. Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your computer. We use cookies to help us improve your user-experience when using our Site. Cookies are also used to personalize the content you view on the Site. Cookies cannot damages files, does not give access to your computer or any information stored on your computer. Cookies can be accepted or declined at your preference.

**6\. Remarketing**

Remarketing is a method we may use as target advertisement that will display relevant ads tailored based on what has been viewed. If you do not wish to participate in our Remarketing, you have the option to opt out by visiting [Google’s Ads Preferences Manager](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/?sig=ACi0TCh1yimtGw_MCXmyADlHvvNP9ru5SKV9iAKbteqQbUDtboQl0SdUSbwEmoNTXTgnRO-cibkW-SaqoP_hqySYAEFc81F3x_CPdSfJh9l_RsKo6erVcaAnk4XgPtkkyHbV1Pv9yO1rb7AzNUD5rsTct1zzgNfoKIMUxeDT_4FkzCX6sP9tVEyhCzqG6ROQv5tCMf7yyMFhq2MtTRDLTch9bUH9Q9dB0jgIfyeRddAr5tNKR0-C4y20NKYzNXgSDMWONWdq4fSi&hl=en "Google's Ads Preferences Manager"). 

We reserve the right to change this policy from time to time. Please check this page regularly for updates.

You may contact the Privacy Officer by e-mail [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#82f2f0ebf4e3e1fbc2f1f6e7f5e3f0f6efe7e6ebe3ace1edeface3f7), or by regular mail addressed to the Privacy Officer, Stew Art Media (a business of Search Global Pty Ltd), 2a/14 Lionel Road, Mt Waverley, Vic, 3149.
